<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?mso-application progid="Excel.Sheet"?>
<Workbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office"
 xmlns:x="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"
 xmlns:ss="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40">
 <DocumentProperties xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <Author>Owner</Author>
  <LastAuthor>Microsoft Office User</LastAuthor>
  <Created>2019-03-25T03:25:22Z</Created>
  <LastSaved>2019-04-09T22:21:10Z</LastSaved>
  <Version>16.00</Version>
 </DocumentProperties>
 <OfficeDocumentSettings xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <AllowPNG/>
 </OfficeDocumentSettings>
 <ExcelWorkbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
  <WindowHeight>17640</WindowHeight>
  <WindowWidth>29280</WindowWidth>
  <WindowTopX>240</WindowTopX>
  <WindowTopY>460</WindowTopY>
  <ProtectStructure>False</ProtectStructure>
  <ProtectWindows>False</ProtectWindows>
 </ExcelWorkbook>
 <Styles>
  <Style ss:ID="Default" ss:Name="Normal">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
   <Borders/>
   <Font ss:FontName="Calibri" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Size="11" ss:Color="#000000"/>
   <Interior/>
   <NumberFormat/>
   <Protection/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s16">
   <Font ss:FontName="Calibri" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Size="11" ss:Color="#000000"/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s17">
   <Font ss:FontName="Calibri" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Size="11" ss:Color="#222222"/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s18">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom" ss:WrapText="1"/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s19">
   <Font ss:FontName="Calibri" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Color="#000000"/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s21">
   <Interior/>
  </Style>
 </Styles>
 <Worksheet ss:Name="Sheet1">
  <Table ss:ExpandedColumnCount="10" ss:ExpandedRowCount="51" x:FullColumns="1"
   x:FullRows="1" ss:DefaultColumnWidth="53" ss:DefaultRowHeight="15">
   <Column ss:Index="2" ss:Width="275"/>
   <Column ss:Index="5" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="135"/>
   <Column ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="144"/>
   <Column ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="183"/>
   <Column ss:Width="82"/>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">id</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">name</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">director</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">year</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">synopsisshort</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">synopsislong</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">mainactors</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">genre</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">average rating</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">imagefeatured</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">10 Things I hate About You</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Gil Junger</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1999</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">Kat Stratford (Julia Stiles) is  smart and quite abrasive, meaning that she doesn't attract many boys. Unfortunately for her younger sister, Bianca (Larisa Oleynik), house rules say that she can't date until Kat has a boyfriend, so strings are pulled to set Kat up  with handsome new arrival Patrick Verona (Heath Ledger). Will Kat let her guard down enough to fall for the effortlessly charming Patrick?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><ss:Data ss:Type="String"
      xmlns="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40"><Font html:Color="#222222">10 Things I Hate About You is a 1999 American teen romantic comedy-drama is a loose modernization of&#160;</Font><Font
       html:Color="#0B0080">William Shakespeare</Font><Font html:Color="#222222">'s late-16th century comedy&#160;</Font><I><Font
        html:Color="#0B0080">The Taming of the Shrew</Font></I><Font
       html:Color="#222222">, retold in a late-1990s American&#160;</Font><Font
       html:Color="#0B0080">high school</Font><Font html:Color="#222222">&#160;setting. In the story, new student Cameron (Gordon-Levitt) is smitten with Bianca Stratford (Oleynik) and, in order to get around her father's strict rules on&#160;</Font><Font
       html:Color="#0B0080">dating</Font><Font html:Color="#222222">, attempts to get&#160;</Font><Font
       html:Color="#0B0080">bad boy</Font><Font html:Color="#222222">&#160;Patrick (Ledger) to date Bianca's ill-tempered sister, Kat Stratford (Stiles). The film is titled after a poem written by Kat about her bittersweet romance with Patrick.</Font></ss:Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s16"><Data ss:Type="String">&#160;Heath Ledger,&#160;Julia Stiles,&#160;Joseph Gordon-Levitt&#160;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">romance, comedy, teen</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">A Good Year</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ridley Scott</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2006</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">London banker Max Skinner (Russell Crowe) inherits his uncle's (Albert Finney) vineyard in Provence, where he spent many childhood holidays. Upon his arrival, he meets a woman from California who tells Max she is his long-lost cousin and that the property is hers.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">After years of no contact with his Uncle Henry, London banker and bond trader Max Skinner learns that Henry has died intestate, so Max inherits a château and vineyard in Provence. Max had spent parts of his childhood there, learning maxims , how to win and lose, and honing his killer instinct (at chess, which serves him well in finance). Max goes to France intent on selling the property. However he spends a few days there, getting the property ready to show. Memories, a beautiful woman, and a young American who says she's Henry's illegitimate daughter interrupt his plans. Did Max the boy know things that Max the man has forgotten?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s19"><Data ss:Type="String">&#160;Russell Crowe,&#160;Abbie Cornish,&#160;Albert Finney</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">romance, comedy, drama</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">A Knights Tale</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Brian Helgeland</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2001</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s17"><Data ss:Type="String">Peasant-born William Thatcher (Heath Ledger) begins a quest to change his stars, win the heart of an exceedingly fair maiden (Shanynn Sossamon) and rock his medieval world. With the help of friends (Mark Addy, Paul Bettany, Alan Tudyk), he faces the ultimate test of medieval gallantry &#45;- tournament jousting &#45;- and tries to discover if he has the mettle to become a legend.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Inspired by &quot;The Canterbury Tales,&quot; as well as the early life of William Marshall (later First Earl of Pembroke), this is the story of William, a young squire with a gift for jousting. After his master dies suddenly, the squire hits the road with his cohorts Roland and Wat. On the journey, they stumble across an unknown writer, Chaucer. William, lacking a proper pedigree, convinces Chaucer to forge genealogy documents that will pass him off as a knight. With his newly-minted history in hand, the young man sets out to prove himself a worthy knight at the country's jousting competition, and finds romance along the way.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Heath Ledger, Rufus Sewell, Shannyn Sossamon</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">action, history, drama</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Anastasia</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Don Bluth,&#160;Gary Goldman</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1997</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The daughter of the last Russian Tsar, Nicolas II, Anastasia is found by two Russian con men, Dimitri and Vladimir, who seek the reward that her grandmother, the Dowager Empress Marie, promised to the ones who'll find her. But the evil mystic of the Tsar family, Rasputin, still wants the Romanov family to be destroyed forever.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The evil wizard Rasputin (Christopher Lloyd) puts a hex on the royal Romanovs and young Anastasia (Meg Ryan) disappears when their palace is overrun. Years later, the Grand Duchess (Angela Lansbury) offers a reward for Anastasia's return. Two scheming Russians (John Cusack, Kelsey Grammer), planning to pawn off a phony, hold auditions and choose an orphan girl with a remarkable resemblance to the missing princess. They bring her to Paris for the reward, not knowing she's the real Anastasia.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"> Meg Ryan, Christopher Llyod, John Cusack</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">family, drama</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">5</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Avatar</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">James Cameron</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2009</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">On the lush alien world of Pandora live the Na'vi, beings who appear primitive but are highly evolved. Because the planet's environment is poisonous, human/Na'vi hybrids, called Avatars, must link to human minds to allow for free movement on Pandora. Jake Sully (Sam Worthington), a paralyzed former Marine, becomes mobile again through one such Avatar and falls in love with a Na'vi woman (Zoe Saldana). As a bond with her grows, he is drawn into a battle for the survival of her world.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">When his brother is killed in a robbery, paraplegic Marine Jake Sully decides to take his place in a mission on the distant world of Pandora. There he learns of greedy corporate figurehead Parker Selfridge's intentions of driving off the native humanoid &quot;Na'vi&quot; in order to mine for the precious material scattered throughout their rich woodland. In exchange for the spinal surgery that will fix his legs, Jake gathers intel for the cooperating military unit spearheaded by gung-ho Colonel Quaritch, while simultaneously attempting to infiltrate the Na'vi people with the use of an &quot;avatar&quot; identity. While Jake begins to bond with the native tribe and quickly falls in love with the beautiful alien Neytiri, the restless Colonel moves forward with his ruthless extermination tactics, forcing the soldier to take a stand - and fight back in an epic battle for the fate of Pandora.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Zoe Saldana, Sam worthington, Stephen Lang</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Sci-fi, Action, Fantasy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">6</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Balto </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Simon Wells</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1995</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">An outcast half-wolf risks his life to prevent a deadly epidemic from ravaging Nome, Alaska.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In this animated feature, a deadly diphtheria epidemic strikes the remote town of Nome, Alaska. With the life-saving medicine located hundreds of miles away, the residents decide to send out a sled-dog team. Balto (Kevin Bacon) &#45;- a half-wolf dog ignored by all except a goose, Boris (Bob Hoskins), and two polar bears &#45;- is chosen to run but is disqualified by lead dog Steele (Jim Cummings). When the other dogs get lost in the snow, Balto risks his life to rescue them and deliver the medicine.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Kevin Bacon, Bridget Fonda, Bob Hoskins</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">family, history</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">balto.png</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">7</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bee Movie</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Simon J Smith, Stephen Hickner</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2007</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Fresh out of college, Barry the Bee (Jerry Seinfeld) finds the prospect of working with honey uninspiring. He flies outside the hive for the first time and talks to a human (Renée Zellweger), breaking a cardinal rule of his species. Barry learns that humans have been stealing and eating honey for centuries, and he realizes that his true calling is to obtain justice for his kind by suing humanity for theft.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Does good necessarily follow good intentions? Barry B. Benson, a bee who's just finished his education and hates the idea of picking a life-long vocation, meets a human, florist Vanessa Bloom, while buzzing about Manhattan. She takes him to a supermarket where Barry discovers shelves and shelves of honey. Realizing it has been taken from bees - who work tirelessly and exhaust themselves for their two cups a year - he follows the delivery truck back to the honey farm, gathers evidence, and files suit against humanity. But what if Barry wins and the honey is returned to the bees, who can then slack off? An ecological cataclysm?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"> Jerry Seinfeld, Patrick Warburton, Renée Zellweger</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">family, comedy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">beemovie.png</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">8</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Beverly Hills Chihuahua</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Raja Gosnell</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2008</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Chloe (Drew Barrymore), a pampered Chihuahua from Beverly Hills, gets an unwelcome taste of the real world when she gets lost in a tough part of Mexico. With no Rodeo Drive boutiques in sight, she is out of her element, until scrappy street dogs Delgado and Papi lend her a paw, helping her find her way home.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Chloe, a diamond-clad ultra-pampered Beverly Hills Chihuahua finds herself being &quot;puppy-sit&quot; by the niece, Rachel, of her owner when she leaves for Europe for one of her fashion shows. Rachel is enjoying her aunt's wealthy home but can't resist a weekend trip to Mexico with her friends. With Chloe in tote, Rachel's partying quickly disgusts Chloe and she decides she will go home herself. Chloe quickly gets lost in Mexico and thrown into a dog-fighting ring where she meets Delgado, an ex police K9 who is there and finds himself between his old enemy Diablo, the drug-lord's dog who ruined his career, and Chloe. After saving her and himself, Delgado agrees to help her get home and they begin their journey across Mexico for Beverly Hills. Meanwhile, Rachel has enlisted the help of her Aunt's gardener and Papi, the gardener's Chihuahua who's crazy about Chloe, to help find and save her. At the same time Diablo's master has learned of Chloe's identity and plans on dog-napping her for a big ransom. Along the way Chloe learns of her ancestry, her own strengths, and also finds a little love.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Drew Barrymore, Andy Garcia, Jamie Lee Curtis</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">family, comedy, romance</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1.5</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">bcubanner.png</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">9</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Cat in the Hat</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bo Welch</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2003</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In this live-action film based on the favorite children's tale, the trouble-making Cat in the Hat (Mike Myers) arrives at the home of bored young Sally Walden (Dakota Fanning) and her brother, Conrad (Spencer Breslin), while their mother (Kelly Preston) is out. The family's pet fish (Sean Hayes) objects to the Cat's presence, but that doesn't stop the hat-wearing giant feline from trying to have fun, no matter how much destruction is left in his wake.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mike Myers stars in the title role as the mischievous feline with the red-and-white striped magical stovepipe hat, a film adaptation of the beloved Dr. Seuss book, `The Cat in the Hat'. The Cat stirs up mischief wherever he goes, especially for Conrad and Sally Walden, (Spencer Breslin and Dakota Fanning) two children who are home alone with their pet fish. With nothing to do, Conrad begins to mess-up the house by riding a board down the stairs. Their single mom (Kelly Preston) is having the company party that night, and the house must be neat and clean or her germ-o-phobic boss will fire her. She orders the children not to take one step into the living room. Of course, when the Cat arrives, he is part of a wrecking crew that destroys the house.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mike Myers, Dakota Fanning, Spencer Breslin</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">family, comedy, fantasy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">10</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Crazy Stupid Love</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Glenn Ficarra, John Requa</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2011</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Cal Weaver (Steve Carell) is living the American dream. He has a good job, a beautiful house, great children and a beautiful wife, named Emily (Julianne Moore). Cal's seemingly perfect life unravels, however, when he learns that Emily has been unfaithful and wants a divorce. Over 40 and suddenly single, Cal is adrift in the fickle world of dating. Enter, Jacob Palmer (Ryan Gosling), a self-styled player who takes Cal under his wing and teaches him how to be a hit with the ladies.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Cal and Emily have been married for over 20 years. But when Cal learns that Emily had an affair he moves out. He would then go to a bar and whine about what happened. Jacob, a regular at the bar, upon hearing his woes offers to help him. By giving him a makeover and teaching him how to be a player. It isn't long before he's picking up someone frequently. But eventually he realizes he still loves Emily and wishes he could go back. At the same time his son is nursing a crush on his baby sitter who doesn't feel the same way. And even Jacob gets a new outlook when starts to feel something about a girl he tried to pick up earlier, but turned him down because she has a boyfriend.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Steve Carrell, Ryan Gosling, Emma Stone</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">comedy, romance, drama</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="13.5">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">11</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Dumbo</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ben Sharpsteen, Norm Ferguson, Wilfred Jackson, Jack Kinney, Samuel Armstrong, Bill Roberts, John Elliotte</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1941</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">A young circus elephant is born with comically large ears and given the cruel nickname Dumbo. One day at a show, he is taunted by a group of kids, inciting his mother into a rage that gets her locked up. After Dumbo's ears cause an accident that injures many of the other elephants, he is made to dress like a clown and perform dangerous stunts. Everything changes when Dumbo discovers that his enormous ears actually allow him to fly, and he astounds everyone at the circus with his new talent.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The shortest of Disney's major animated features Dumbo involves a baby elephant with unusually large ears. Ostracized from the rest of the circus animals, poor Dumbo is even separated from his mother, who is chained up in a separate cage after trying to defend her child. Only brash-but-lovable Timothy Mouse offers the hand of friendship to Dumbo, encouraging the pachyderm to exploit his &quot;different&quot; qualities for fame and fortune. After indulging in a vat of booze, Dumbo awakens in a tall tree. Goaded by a group of jive-talking crows, Dumbo discovers that his out-sized ears have given him the ability to fly.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Hall Johnson Choir, Willfried Herbst, Inge Wolffberg</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">family, fantasy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="13.5">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">12</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Eight below</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Frank Marshall</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2006</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The frozen wasteland of Antarctica serves as the background for a tale about the bonds of friendship and loyalty. Three members of a scientific expedition, Jerry Shepard (Paul Walker), his friend Cooper (Jason Biggs) and an American geologist (Bruce Greenwood), must leave their beloved sled dogs behind after a devastating accident and increasingly perilous weather conditions. Alone, the dogs struggle to survive the harsh Antarctic winter.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s18"><Data ss:Type="String">In the Antarctic, after an expedition with Dr. Davis McClaren, the sled dog trainer Jerry Shepherd has to leave the polar base with his colleagues due to the proximity of a heavy snow storm. He ties his dogs to be rescued after, but the mission is called-off and the dogs are left alone at their own fortune. For six months,&#10;the temporary evacuation becomes permanent (through the winter season) and Jerry becomes fixated on returning to the dogs, not knowing if they are dead or alive and tries to find a sponsor for a rescue mission while his dogs fight for survival.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Paul Walker, Moon Boodgood, Bruce Greenwood</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">drama, family</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">eightbelow.png</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">13</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Extremely Loud &amp; Incredibly Close</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Stephen Daldry</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2011</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Oskar (Thomas Horn), who lost his father (Tom Hanks) in the 9/11 attack on the World Trade Center, is convinced that his dad left a final message for him somewhere in the city. Upon finding a mysterious key in his father's closet, Oskar sets out in search of the lock it fits. Feeling disconnected from his grieving mother (Sandra Bullock) and driven by a tirelessly active mind, Oskar has a journey of discovery that takes him beyond his loss and leads to a greater understanding of the world.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The film begins with a body that seems to be falling from the sky, referencing jumpers from the World Trade Center on September 11. Oskar Schell (Thomas Horn) is introduced as the son of German American Thomas Schell (Tom Hanks).As troubled young boy, Oskar, is trying to cope with the loss of his father. Oskar starts lashing out at his mother and the world. Until a year later, he discovers a mysterious key in his father's belongings and embarks on a scavenger hunt to find the matching lock, just as he used to when his father was alive. On this journey he is bound to meet a lot of people and learn a lot about himself and his family, but will he ever find the lock?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Thomas Horn, Tom Hanks, Sandra Bullock</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">drama, mystery</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">14</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Forgetting Sarah Marshall</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Nicholas Stoller</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2008</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Struggling musician Peter Bretter (Jason Segel) is better-known as the boyfriend of TV star Sarah Marshall (Kristen Bell). After she unceremoniously dumps him, he feels lost and alone but makes a last-ditch bid to get over it by going to Hawaii. However, she and her new boyfriend (Russell Brand) are there in the same hotel.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Peter is a composer and a likable sad sack who's devastated when his girlfriend of five years, Sarah Marshall, the star of a cheesy CSI-style crime show, dumps him. He weeps, he rails, he mopes. Finally, his step-brother Brian suggests Hawaii, so Peter heads for a resort on Oahu where, as he's checking in, he sees Sarah and her new beau, Aldous, a polymorphously perverse English rocker. The weeping and moping start again, until Peter is rescued by Rachel, a thoughtful hotel clerk who invites him to a luau and to hang out. Although he constantly runs into Sarah and Aldous, Peter starts to come alive again. Will Sarah realize what she's lost, and what about Rachel?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Jason Segel, Rusel Brand, Kristen Bell</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">comedy, drama</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">15</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Gladiator</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ridley Scott</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2000</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Set in Roman times, the story of a once-powerful general forced to become a common gladiator. The emperor's son is enraged when he is passed over as heir in favour of his father's favourite general. He kills his father and arranges the murder of the general's family, and the general is sold into slavery to be trained as a gladiator - but his subsequent popularity in the arena threatens the throne.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In 180 A.D. Rome, the weary and dying emperor, Marcus Aurelius, names his loyal and triumphant general, Maximus Decimus Meridius, his successor and protector of Rome, much to the dismay of his haughty and unbalanced son, Commodus. But, instead, death and entrapment await, as the embittered and blind with rage rival rewards Rome's hero with an order for his execution, only to wind up as a slave to the former gladiator, Proximo. From the vast deserts of North Africa, a new Maximo will rise as a gladiator, hacking and slashing his way through all the way up to Mother Rome and the unsuspecting dictator, Commodus. But will the popular general ever find peace in a long-awaited retribution?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Russel Crowe, Joaquin Pheonix, Connie Nielson</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">history, drama, action</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">16</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Chris Columbus</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2002</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The second instalment of boy wizard Harry Potter's adventures at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry, based on the novel by JK Rowling. A mysterious elf tells Harry to expect trouble during his second year at Hogwarts, but nothing can prepare him for trees that fight back, flying cars, spiders that talk and deadly warnings written in blood on the walls of the school.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Forced to spend his summer holidays with his muggle relations, Harry Potter gets a real shock when he gets a surprise visitor: Dobby the house-elf, who warns Harry Potter against returning to Hogwarts, for terrible things are going to happen. Harry decides to ignore Dobby's warning and continues with his pre-arranged schedule. But at Hogwarts, strange and terrible things are indeed happening. Harry is suddenly hearing mysterious voices from inside the walls, muggle-born students are being attacked, and a message scrawled on the wall in blood puts everyone on his or her guard, &quot;The Chamber Of Secrets Has Been Opened. Enemies Of The Heir, Beware&quot; .</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Daniel Radcliffe, Emma watson, Rupert Grint</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">fantasy, family, action</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">f</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">17</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Indiana Jones and the Tale of the Crystal Skull</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Steven Spielberg</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2008</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In 1957, archaeologist and adventurer Dr. Henry &quot;Indiana&quot; Jones, Jr. is called back into action and becomes entangled in a Soviet plot to uncover the secret behind mysterious artifacts known as the Crystal Skulls.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">During the Cold War, Soviet agents watch Professor Henry Jones when a young man brings him a coded message from an aged, demented colleague, Harold Oxley. Led by the brilliant Irina Spalko, the Soviets tail Jones and the young man, Mutt, to Peru. With Oxley's code, they find a legendary skull made of a single piece of quartz. If Jones can deliver the skull to its rightful place, all may be well; but if Irina takes it to its origin, she'll gain powers that could endanger the West. Aging professor and young buck join forces with a woman from Jones' past to face the dangers of the jungle, Russia, and the supernatural.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Harrison Ford, Cat Blanchet, Shia Lebouf</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">action, drama</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">18</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">John Carter</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Andrew Stanton</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2012</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">When Civil War veteran John Carter (Taylor Kitsch) mysteriously awakes on the surface of Mars &#45;- also called Barsoom &#45;- he little expects the adventure that awaits him. Carter reluctantly becomes embroiled in an epic conflict among the red planet's inhabitants, including Tars Tarkas (Willem Dafoe) and Princess Dejah Thoris (Lynn Collins). As Barsoom is poised on the brink of collapse, war-weary Carter rediscovers his humanity when he realizes that everyone's fate is in his hands.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">John Carter, a Civil War veteran, who in 1868 was trying to live a normal life, is &quot;asked&quot; by the Army to join, but he refuses so he is locked up. He escapes, and is pursued. Eventually they run into some Indians, and there's a gunfight. Carter seeks refuge in a cave. While there, he encounters someone who is holding some kind of medallion. When Carter touches it, he finds himself in a place where he can leap incredible heights, among other things. He later encounters beings he has never seen before. He meets a woman who helps him to discover that he is on Mars, and he learns there's some kind of unrest going on.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">taylor Kitsch, Lynn Collins, William Dafoe</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">fantasy, sci-fi, action</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">m</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">19</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Kill Bill</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Quentin Tarantino</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2003</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">A former assassin, known simply as The Bride (Uma Thurman), wakes from a coma four years after her jealous ex-lover Bill (David Carradine) attempts to murder her on her wedding day. Fueled by an insatiable desire for revenge, she vows to get even with every person who contributed to the loss of her unborn child, her entire wedding party, and four years of her life. After devising a hit list, The Bride sets off on her quest, enduring unspeakable injury and unscrupulous enemies.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The lead character, called 'The Bride,' was a member of the Deadly Viper Assassination Squad, led by her lover 'Bill.' Upon realizing she was pregnant with Bill's child, 'The Bride' decided to escape her life as a killer. She fled to Texas, met a young man, who, on the day of their wedding rehearsal was gunned down by an angry and jealous Bill (with the assistance of the Deadly Viper Assassination Squad). Four years later, 'The Bride' wakes from a coma, and discovers her baby is gone. She, then, decides to seek revenge upon the five people who destroyed her life and killed her baby. The saga of Kill Bill Volume I begins.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Um Thurman, Dad Carradine, Lucy Liu</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">action, drama, comedy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">killbill.png</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">20</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">King Arthur: Legend of the Sword</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Guy Ritchie</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2017</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">After the murder of his father, young Arthur's power-hungry uncle Vortigern seizes control of the crown. Robbed of his birthright, he grows up the hard way in the back alleys of the city, not knowing who he truly is. When fate leads him to pull the Excalibur sword from stone, Arthur embraces his true destiny to become a legendary fighter and leader.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">An alternative version of the King Arthur legend. As a boy, Arthur is left orphaned after his father, King Uther Pendragon, and mother are killed in a war waged against them by Vortigern, who then assumes the throne. Arthur flees and is raised in a brothel, knowing very little of his birthright. Vortigern wants Arthur dead, to ensure there is no claimant to the throne. The legends foretell that only the next king will be able to draw Excalibur, Uther's sword, from the rock where it is lodged. So, in an effort to identify Arthur, Vortigern forces all the young men of Arthur's age to attempt to draw out the sword. Now it is Arthur's turn.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Charlie Hunnam, Jude law, Eric Bana</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">action, fantasy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">21</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Peter Jackson</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2001</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The future of civilization rests in the fate of the One Ring, which has been lost for centuries. Powerful forces are unrelenting in their search for it. But fate has placed it in the hands of a young Hobbit named Frodo Baggins (Elijah Wood), who inherits the Ring and steps into legend. A daunting task lies ahead for Frodo when he becomes the Ringbearer - to destroy the One Ring in the fires of Mount Doom where it was forged.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">An ancient Ring thought lost for centuries has been found, and through a strange twist of fate has been given to a small Hobbit named Frodo. When Gandalf discovers the Ring is in fact the One Ring of the Dark Lord Sauron, Frodo must make an epic quest to the Cracks of Doom in order to destroy it. However, he does not go alone. He is joined by Gandalf, Legolas the elf, Gimli the Dwarf, Aragorn, Boromir, and his three Hobbit friends Merry, Pippin, and Samwise. Through mountains, snow, darkness, forests, rivers and plains, facing evil and danger at every corner the Fellowship of the Ring must go. Their quest to destroy the One Ring is the only hope for the end of the Dark Lords reign.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Elijah Wood, Andy Serkis, Viggo Mortensen</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">action, fantasy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">22</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Mary Poppins</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Robert Stevenson</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1964</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In Edwardian London's Cherry Tree Lane, yet another nanny resigns from keeping an eye on Mr Banks' boisterous children, Jane and Michael. But then, as if by magic, a new governess&#45;-the enchanting, Mary Poppins&#45;-lands on their doorstep to take control of the situation, as thrilling adventures along with the amazing chimney sweep, Bert, pave the way for a wonderful transformation. Will the charming Miss Poppins turn chaos into order?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">When Jane (Karen Dotrice) and Michael (Matthew Garber), the children of the wealthy and uptight Banks family, are faced with the prospect of a new nanny, they are pleasantly surprised by the arrival of the magical Mary Poppins (Julie Andrews). Embarking on a series of fantastical adventures with Mary and her Cockney performer friend, Bert (Dick Van Dyke), the siblings try to pass on some of their nanny's sunny attitude to their preoccupied parents (David Tomlinson, Glynis Johns).</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Dick Van Dyke, Julie Andrews, Karen Dotrice</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">fantasy, family, action</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">marypoppins.png</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">23</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Narnia Prince Caspian</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Andrew Adamson</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2008</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">One year after their previous adventure, the Pevensie children (Georgie Henley, Skandar Keynes, William Moseley, Anna Popplewell) return to the magical land of Narnia and find that 1300 years have passed there. War has come to Narnia once again, and the children join forces with Prince Caspian (Ben Barnes) to overthrow the evil King Miraz and restore peace to the land.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">A year has passed by since the Pevensie children stepped through the wardrobe. In Narnia, centuries have passed since the defeat of the White Witch. Now the foursome are sent back to Narnia to find that everything was destroyed and the Narnia they once knew is gone forever. They come to aid the young Prince Caspian, who is leading a group of Old Narnians to wage war against his malicious uncle Miraz, who rules Narnia with an iron fist. Will they succeed? When will Aslan return?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Anna Popplewell, Georgie Henley, Wlliam Mosely</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">fantasy, action</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">24</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Narnia the Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Andrew Adamson</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2005</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Four kids travel through a wardrobe to the land of Narnia and learn of their destiny to free it with the guidance of a mystical lion.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">During the World War II bombings of London, four English siblings are sent to a country house where they will be safe. One day Lucy (Georgie Henley) finds a wardrobe that transports her to a magical world called Narnia. After coming back, she soon returns to Narnia with her brothers, Peter (William Moseley) and Edmund (Skandar Keynes), and her sister, Susan (Anna Popplewell). There they join the magical lion, Aslan (Liam Neeson), in the fight against the evil White Witch, Jadis (Tilda Swinton).</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ben Barnes, Georgie Henley, Wlliam Mosely</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">fantasy, action</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">25</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Nims Island</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Jennifer Flackett, Mark Levin</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2008</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Life is an adventure for a courageous youngster named Nim (Abigail Breslin), who lives on an exotic island with her marine-biologist father. and a menagerie of animal friends. When Nim's father goes missing, she turns to the only person she knows who can help her: adventurer Alex Rover (Gerard Butler). But what she doesn't know is that Alex Rover is really Alexandra (Jodie Foster), a timid recluse. Though faint of heart, Alexandra must find the courage within herself to come to Nim's aid.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Nim Rusoe is a girl who joins her father, a scientist, when he does research on marine life on an island. It's just the two of them but she spends her time making friends with all the animals she encounters, chatting on the computer and reading the adventure books of Alex Rover. When her father goes to do some research but when a storm strikes the island he doesn't come back, she gets worried and frightened. She then e-mails Alex Rover hoping that he will come but what she doesn't know is that Alex Rover is a woman who is agoraphobic and germaphobic. But her creation comes to life and eggs her to go. Unfortunately she has never gone anywhere before and is denied her necessities like her sanitary gel by the customs officer at the airport. In the meantime, Nim tries to be strong while waiting for Alex to arrive.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Jodie Foster, Abigail Breslin, Gerald Butler</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">fantasy, family</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">26</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Oceans Eleven</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Steven Soderbergh</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2001</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Dapper Danny Ocean (George Clooney) is a man of action. Less than 24 hours into his parole from a New Jersey penitentiary, the wry, charismatic thief is already rolling out his next plan. Following three rules: Don't hurt anybody, don't steal from anyone who doesn't deserve it, and play the game like you've got nothing to lose. Danny orchestrates the most sophisticated, elaborate casino heist in history.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Danny Ocean is a thief who has just been paroled from prison. He seeks out his partner, Rusty and he has a job. And it is to rob the vault that houses the cash of three casinos in Las Vegas. And he plans to rob it on a night when 150 million is in it. So they recruit nine guys and they begin to put Ocean's plan in motion. Everything is going well until Rusty discovers that Ocean's ex-wife, Tess is the main squeeze of Terry Benedict the (ruthless) owner of the casinos. Rusty asks him what is he going to do if he has to choose. But Ocean says that if his plan goes smoothly, he is going to be able to have his cake and eat it.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">George Clooney, Matt Damon, Brad Pitt</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">crime, heist, mystery</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">27</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Peter Pan</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">P J Hogan</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2003</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Darling family children receive a visit from Peter Pan, who takes them to Never Land where an ongoing war with the evil Pirate Captain Hook is taking place.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">As Wendy Darling (Rachel Hurd-Wood) recounts stories to her brothers, John (Harry Newell) and Michael (Freddie Popplewell), she is visited by Peter Pan (Jeremy Sumpter). Peter, a boy who magically never ages, invites Wendy and her brothers to Neverland, an island where he lives with the Lost Boys. Once there, however, Wendy and her brothers are kidnapped by Captain Hook (Jason Isaacs). Peter, with assistance from the fairy Tink (Ludivine Sagnier), must face Hook in order to rescue the Darlings.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Jeremy Sumpter, Rachel Hurd-Wood, jason Isaacs</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">fantasy, family</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">28</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Piglets Big Movie</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Francis Glebas</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2003</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">When the gang from the Hundred Acre Wood begin a honey harvest, young Piglet is excluded and told that he is too small to help. Feeling inferior, Piglet disappears and his pals Eeyore, Rabbit, Tigger, Roo, and Winnie the Pooh must use Piglet's scrapbook as a map to find him. In the process they discover that this very small animal has been a big hero in a lot of ways.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In this animated feature, Piglet (John Fiedler) is the smallest of all his friends, which doesn't account for his big heart and bold attitude. But, try as he might, Piglet cannot convey his personality to his friends &#45;- not even to Winnie the Pooh (Jim Cummings) ! Piglet becomes fed up after being excluded from a honey-thieving scheme, so strikes out on his own to do some thinking. But when Piglet's friends discover he's missing, the only clue they have to go on is a scrapbook he left behind.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">John Fielder, Jim Cummings, Peter Cullen</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">family, drama</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">29</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pocohontas</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Eric Goldberg, Mike Gabriel</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1995</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">This is the Disney animated tale of the romance between a young American Indian woman named Pocahontas (Irene Bedard) and Capt. John Smith (Mel Gibson), who journeyed to the New World with other settlers to begin fresh lives. Her powerful father, Chief Powhatan, disapproves of their relationship and wants her to marry a native warrior. Meanwhile, Smith's fellow Englishmen hope to rob the Native Americans of their gold. Can Pocahontas' love for Smith save the day?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Capt. John Smith leads a rag-tag band of English sailors &amp; soldiers to the New World to plunder its riches for England (or, more precisely, for Governor Ratcliffe, who comes along for the ride). Meanwhile, in this &quot;New World,&quot; Chief Powhatan has pledged his daughter, Pocahontas, to be married to the village's greatest warrior. Pocahontas, however, has other ideas. She has seen a vision of a spinning arrow, a vision she believes tells her change is coming. Her life does indeed change when the English ship lands near her village. Between Ratcliffe, who believes the &quot;savages&quot; are hiding the gold he expected to be plentiful, and Powhatan, who believes these pale newcomers will destroy their land, Smith and Pocahontas have a difficult time preventing all-out war, and saving their love for each other.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Irene Bedard, Christian Bale, Mel Gibson</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">family, drama, romance</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">30</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pretty Woman</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Gary Marshall</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1990</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In this modern update on Cinderella, a prostitute and a wealthy businessman fall hard for one another, forming an unlikely pair. While on a business trip in L.A., Edward (Richard Gere), who makes a living buying and breaking up companies, picks up a hooker, Vivian (Julia Roberts), on a lark. After Edward hires Vivian to stay with him for the weekend, the two get closer, only to discover there are significant hurdles to overcome as they try to bridge the gap between their very different worlds.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">High-powered businessman Edward Lewis has broken up with his girlfriend after an unpleasant phone call wherein he asked her to escort him during his business trip - she is offended that he treats her as his &quot;beck and call girl&quot;. Edward is a corporate raider, who buys companies that are in financial trouble and tears down the company piece by piece. Leaving a business party in the Hollywood Hills, he takes his lawyer's Lotus Esprit sports car, and accidentally ends up on Hollywood Boulevard in the city's red-light district, where he encounters prostitute Vivian Ward.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Julia Roberts, Richard Gere, Hector Elizondo</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">romance, comedy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">31</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pride and Predjudice</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Joe Wright</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2005</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In this adaptation of Jane Austen's beloved novel, Elizabeth Bennet (Keira Knightley) lives with her mother, father and sisters in the English countryside. As the eldest, she faces mounting pressure from her parents to marry. When the outspoken Elizabeth is introduced to the handsome and upper-class Mr. Darcy (Matthew MacFadyen), sparks fly. Although there is obvious chemistry between the two, Darcy's overly reserved nature threatens the fledgling relationship.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">This tale of love and values unfolds in the class-conscious England of the late 18th century. The five Bennet sisters - including strong-willed Elizabeth and young Lydia - have been raised by their mother with one purpose in life: finding a husband. When a wealthy bachelor takes up residence in a nearby mansion, the Bennets are abuzz. Amongst the man's sophisticated circle of friends, surely there will be no shortage of suitors for the Bennet sisters. But when Elizabeth meets up with the handsome and - it would seem - snobbish Mr. Darcy, the battle of the sexes is joined.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Keira Knighty, Mathew Macfayden, Rosamind Pike</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">romance, history, drama</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">32</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Robin Hood</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ridley Scott</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2012</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">After the death of Richard the Lion-Hearted, a skilled archer named Robin Longstride (Russell Crowe) travels to Nottingham, where villagers suffer under a despotic sheriff and crippling taxation. He meets and falls in love with a spirited widow, Marion (Cate Blanchett), although she is skeptical of his motives. Hoping to win her heart and save the village, Robin gathers a band of warriors to fight corruption in Nottingham, little knowing they will soon be fighting to save England itself.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Birth of a legend. Following King Richard's death in France, archer Robin Longstride, along with Will Scarlett, Alan-a-Dale and Little John, returns to England. They encounter the dying Robert of Locksley, whose party was ambushed by treacherous Godfrey, who hopes to facilitate a French invasion of England. Robin promises the dying knight he will return his sword to his father Walter in Nottingham. Here Walter encourages him to impersonate the dead man to prevent his land being confiscated by the crown, and he finds himself with Marian, a ready-made wife. Hoping to stir baronial opposition to weak King John and allow an easy French take-over, Godfrey worms his way into the king's service as Earl Marshal of England and brutally invades towns under the pretext of collecting Royal taxes. Can Robin navigate the politics of barons, royals, traitors, and the French?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Russel Crowe, Cate Blanchett, Oscar Isaac</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">drama, action, history</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">33</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Robots</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Chris Wedge, Carlos Saldanha</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2005</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In a world of sentient robots, striving young inventor Rodney Copperbottom (Ewan McGregor) wants to work for the avuncular Bigweld (Mel Brooks), whose Bigweld Industries makes spare robot parts. But Bigweld has just been deposed as company head by the villainous Phineas T. Ratchet (Greg Kinnear), who wants to make all robots submit to profitable forced upgrades. In this animated adventure, Rodney and his friend Fender (Robin Williams) go underground to fight Ratchet's evil plans.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Even in a world populated entirely by mechanical beings Rodney Copperbottom is considered a genius inventor. Rodney dreams of two things, making the world a better place and meeting his idol, the master inventor Bigweld. On his journey he encounters Cappy, a beautiful executive 'bot with whom Rodney is instantly smitten, the nefarious corporate tyrant Ratchet who locks horns with Rodney, and a group of misfit 'bots known as the Rusties, led by Fender and Piper Pinwheeler.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Chris Wedge, Robin Williams, Halle Berry</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">romance, family</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">34</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Rock Of Ages</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Adam Shankman</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2012</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The songs of Journey, Bon Jovi, Def Leppard and other artists underscore a tale of big dreams in Hollywood. Soon after hopping off a bus from the Midwest, aspiring singer Sherrie Christian (Julianne Hough) immediately finds herself in trouble. Coming to her rescue is Drew (Diego Boneta), a bar-back at the legendary club the Bourbon Room. With stars in their eyes, the young lovers chase their dreams, but a misunderstanding involving rock god Stacee Jaxx (Tom Cruise) threatens to tear them apart</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1987. Naive Sherrie Christian has just arrived in Hollywood from Tulsa looking to become a rock star. She is just likel Drew Boley was when he first arrived in Hollywood, he, now the Hollywood veteran, who works as ia bar back at the Bourbon Club, known as the center of the rock scene in town and the place where many of the biggest acts in rociiiiki got their big break. The two meet as Drew helps Sherrie with a situation when she first arrives in town. IDespite Dennis Dupree, the Bourbon's owner/manager, not liiking to hire people like Drew or Sherrie - someone who has musical aspirations - as service staff, Drew is able to convince Dennis and his assistant Lonny to hire Sherrie as a server, Drew and Sherrie who have a blossoming mutual attraction. Dennis and Lonny, who are having financial difficulties, are able to convince rock star Stacee Jaxx, the perpetually stoned front man for the band Arsenal who got his first break performing at the Bourbon, to perform for free at a benefit concert at the club. </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Tom Cruise, Julianne Hough, Alec baldwin</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">history, drama, comedy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">35</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Shrek</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Andrew Adamson, Vicky Jenson</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2001</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Once upon a time, in a far away swamp, there lived an ogre named Shrek (Mike Myers) whose precious solitude is suddenly shattered by an invasion of annoying fairy tale characters. They were all banished from their kingdom by the evil Lord Farquaad (John Lithgow). Determined to save their home &#45;- not to mention his &#45;- Shrek cuts a deal with Farquaad and sets out to rescue Princess Fiona (Cameron Diaz) to be Farquaad's bride. Rescuing the Princess may be small compared to her deep, dark secret.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">When a green ogre named Shrek discovers his swamp has been 'swamped' with all sorts of fairytale creatures by the scheming Lord Farquaad, Shrek sets out with a very loud donkey by his side to 'persuade' Farquaad to give Shrek his swamp back. Instead, a deal is made. Farquaad, who wants to become the King, sends Shrek to rescue Princess Fiona, who is awaiting her true love in a tower guarded by a fire-breathing dragon. But once they head back with Fiona, it starts to become apparent that not only does Shrek, an ugly ogre, begin to fall in love with the lovely princess, but Fiona is also hiding a huge secret.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mike Myers, Eddie Murphy, Cameron Diaz</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">fantasy, comedy, family</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">36</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Snatch</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Guy Ritchie</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2000</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Illegal boxing promoter Turkish (Jason Statham) convinces gangster Brick Top (Alan Ford) to offer bets on bare-knuckle boxer Mickey (Brad Pitt) at his bookie business. When Mickey does not throw his first fight as agreed, an infuriated Brick Top demands another match. Meanwhile, gangster Frankie Four Fingers (Benicio Del Toro) comes to place a bet for a friend with Brick Top's bookies, as multiple criminals converge on a stolen diamond that Frankie has come to London to sell.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Turkish and his close friend/accomplice Tommy get pulled into the world of match fixing by the notorious Brick Top. Things get complicated when the boxer they had lined up gets badly beaten by Mickey, a 'pikey' ( slang for an Irish Gypsy)- who comes into the equation after Turkish, an unlicensed boxing promoter wants to buy a caravan off the Irish Gypsies. They then try to convince Mickey not only to fight for them, but to lose for them too. Whilst all this is going on, a huge diamond heist takes place, and a fistful of motley characters enter the story, including 'Cousin Avi', 'Boris The Blade', 'Franky Four Fingers' and 'Bullet Tooth Tony'. Things go from bad to worse as it all becomes about the money, the guns, and the damned dog.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Kevin Statham, Brad Pitt, Benecio Del Torio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">crime, heist, comedy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">37</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Spiderwick Chronicles</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mark Waters</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2008</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Of the three Grace children, Jared (Freddie Highmore) has always been thought of as the troublemaker. So when strange things happen after his family's move to a relative's dilapidated estate, sister Mallory (Sarah Bolger), twin brother Simon and their mother assume that Jared is behind it all. However, magical creatures roam the grounds, and they all want a special book that Jared has found: a field guide to fantastic creatures, penned by Arthur Spiderwick.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Once upon a time, upon moving into the run-down Spiderwick Estate with their mother, twin brothers Jared and Simon Grace, along with their sister Mallory, find themselves pulled into an alternate world full of fairies and other creatures. Unable to explain the strange disappearances and accidents that seem to be happening on a daily basis, the family blames it all on Jared. When he, Simon and Mallory investigate what's really going on, they uncover the fantastic truth of the Spiderwick estate and of the creatures that inhabit it.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Freddie Highmore, Sarah Bolger, Seth Rogen</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">fantasy, family, action</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">38</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Star Wars A New Hope</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">George Lucas</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1977</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Imperial Forces &#45;- under orders from cruel Darth Vader (David Prowse) &#45;- hold Princess Leia (Carrie Fisher) hostage, in their efforts to quell the rebellion against the Galactic Empire. Luke Skywalker (Mark Hamill) and Han Solo (Harrison Ford), captain of the Millennium Falcon, work together with the companionable droid duo R2-D2 (Kenny Baker) and C-3PO (Anthony Daniels) to rescue the beautiful princess, help the Rebel Alliance, and restore freedom and justice to the Galaxy.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Part IV in George Lucas' epic, this movie opens with a rebel ship being boarded by the tyrannical Darth Vader. The plot then follows the life of a simple farm boy, Luke Skywalker, as he and his newly met allies (Han Solo, Chewbacca, Obi-wan Kenobi, C-3PO, R2-D2) attempt to rescue a rebel leader, Princess Leia, from the clutches of the Empire. The conclusion is culminated as the rebels, including Skywalker and flying ace Wedge Antilles make an attack on the Empire's most powerful and ominous weapon, the Death Star.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Harrison Ford, Carrie Fisher, Mark Hamill</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">sci-fi, fantasy, action</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">starwars.png</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">39</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Bourne Identity</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Doug Liman</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2002</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The story of a man (Matt Damon), salvaged, near death, from the ocean by an Italian fishing boat. When he recuperates, the man suffers from total amnesia, without identity or background... except for a range of extraordinary talents in fighting, linguistic skills and self-defense that speak of a dangerous past. He sets out on a desperate search-assisted by the initially rebellious Marie (Franka Potente) - to discover who he really is, and why he's being lethally pursued by assassins.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">On a stormy night, a young man is pulled out of the Mediterranean Sea by the crew of a fishing boat. Thinking the young man is dead, a curious fisherman with a scalpel finds two bullets in his back and a miniature laser device in his hip. The laser reveals a Swiss bank account number. But our wet hero isn't dead, and soon finds himself in Zurich. In the bank vault the young man discovers his name, Jason Bourne. In addition, he finds a baffling pile of different passports, all with his picture, and a huge pile of cash. In the U.S. Embassy, Jason Bourne discovers his love interest and travel partner, Marie, along with the fact that someone wants to kill him. Armed with a bag of money and mysterious martial arts skills, with Marie by his side, Bourne scours Paris for clues about his identity and past life... and finds himself in the middle of two assassination plots masterminded by the CIA.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Matt Damon, Franka Pontete, Julia Stiles</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">action, mystery, heist</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">40</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Green Mile</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Frank Darabont</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1999</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">It's just another normal day on the Green Mile for prison guard Paul Edgecomb. That is until huge John Coffey is sent there. Unlike the hulking brute that Coffey looks like, he is in fact kind at heart. Whilst watching over Coffey, Edgecomb learns that there is more to Coffey than can be seen.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Paul Edgecomb (Tom Hanks) walked the mile with a variety of cons. He had never encountered someone like John Coffey (Michael Clarke Duncan), a massive black man convicted of brutally killing a pair of young sisters. Coffey had the size and strength to kill anyone, but not the demeanor. Beyond his simple, naive nature and a deathly fear of the dark, Coffey seemed to possess a prodigious, supernatural gift. Paul began to question whether Coffey was truly guilty of murdering the two girls.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Michael Clarke Duncan, Tom Hanks, Sam Rockwell</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">drama, fantasy, history</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4.5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">41</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Little Mermaid</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ron Clements, John Musker</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1989</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">This is the story of a little mermaid named Ariel, who dreams of going on land. When her father, King Triton, forbids her to go on land, Ariel visits Ursula who her father had banished. Even though she helps her get to land, what Ariel doesn't know is that Ursula has plans to destroy her to get revenge on her father.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In Disney's beguiling animated romp, rebellious 16-year-old mermaid Ariel (Jodi Benson) is fascinated with life on land. On one of her visits to the surface, which are forbidden by her controlling father, King Triton, she falls for a human prince. Determined to be with her new love, Ariel makes a dangerous deal with the sea witch Ursula (Pat Carroll) to become human for three days. But when plans go awry for the star-crossed lovers, the king must make the ultimate sacrifice for his daughter.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="9"><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">42</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">The Man in the Iron Mask</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Randall Wallace</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1998</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The former musketeer Athos (John Malkovich) swears vengeance after despotic King Louis XIV (Leonardo DiCaprio) causes the death of his son. Summoning his old comrades Porthos (Gérard Depardieu) and Aramis (Jeremy Irons), he hatches a plan to liberate a shackled prisoner rumored to be the king's twin brother, and then install him on the throne. But the three musketeers must also contend with their old friend D'Artagnan (Gabriel Byrne), who has remained in the king's service.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Years have passed since the Three Musketeers, Aramis (Jeremy Irons), Athos (John Malkovich), and Porthos (Gerard Depardieu) fought together with their friend D'Artagnan (Gabriel Byrne). The arrogant, tyrannical King Louis XIV (Leonardo DiCaprio) desires the beautiful Christine (Judith Godreche), so he orders her suitor Raoul (Peter Sarsgaard), the son of Athos, off to face death at the front. He also sends Aramis to kill the leader of a Jesuit rebellion. Louis is unaware that his loyal protector and informant, D'Artagnan, is the secret lover of his mother, Queen Anne (Anne Parillaud). Louis' younger twin brother, Philippe (also DiCaprio) is the man in the iron mask, imprisoned for the past six years. Arthos and Porthos plan to free Philippe, abduct Louis and replace him by putting Philippe on the throne. French location scenes include the Chateau Fontainbleau.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Leonardo DiCaprio, John Malkovich, Jeremy Irons</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">action, mystery, history</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">43</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Shawshank Redemption</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Frank Darabont</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1994</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Andy Dufresne (Tim Robbins) is sentenced to two consecutive life terms in prison for the murders of his wife and her lover and is sentenced to a tough prison. However, only Andy knows he didn't commit the crimes. While there, he forms a friendship with Red (Morgan Freeman), experiences brutality of prison life, adapts, helps the warden, etc., all in 19 years.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bank Merchant Andy Dufresne is convicted of the murder of his wife and her lover, and sentenced to life imprisonment at Shawshank prison. Life seems to have taken a turn for the worse, but fortunately Andy befriends some of the other inmates, in particular a character known only as Red. Over time Andy finds ways to live out life with relative ease as one can in a prison, leaving a message for all that while the body may be locked away in a cell, the spirit can never be truly imprisoned.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Tim Robbins, Morgan Freeman, Bob Gunton</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">drama, mystery, crime</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">5</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">44</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Wind in The Willows</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Dave Unwin</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1995</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mr. Toad (Terry Jones) lives in a mansion, but his obsession with motorcars is taking a toll on his finances. He sells his meadow to the sinister Chief Weasel (Antony Sher), but neglects to tell Mole (Steve Coogan), who lives underneath the field in a cozy burrow. After Mole moves in with his friend Rat (Eric Idle), they learn that Toad is in jail and that his lawyer (John Cleese) is no help. The two friends hatch a plan to find their pal Badger (Nicol Williamson) and free Toad from prison.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">A mole, taken from the fever of spring, comes out of her den, starting a journey with a rat friend on the river and in the woods, where there is the den of the badger and where they spend the lethargy. When the wind blows again in the willows in spring, the three friends leave to change the frog for the better, that is very fickle.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Michael Gambon, Michael Palin, Rik Mayall</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">family, drama,</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">45</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Thunderbirds</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Jonathan Frakes</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2004</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Former astronaut Jeff Tracy (Bill Paxton) runs International Rescue, a top-secret heroic organization, from his headquarters on Tracy Island. The island also houses the futuristic vehicles created by Ray &quot;Brains&quot; Hackenbacker (Anthony Edwards). But while Jeff is on a mission in space, his nemesis, The Hood (Ben Kingsley), invades Tracy Island. The Hood plots to use the island's technology for evil, and only Jeff's son, Alan (Brady Corbet), can stop him.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The year is 2010. Teenager Alan Tracy, sent off to a distant boarding school, is the youngest of the sons of Jeff Tracy, a retired American astronaut. Jeff, a widower, has formed International Rescue, and raised his sons to act as a secret, volunteer organization which uses highly advanced technology to save lives worldwide. Jeff and his older sons John, Virgil, Scott, and Gordon, who like Alan were named after the Mercury Seven astronauts are joined in this effort by Lady Penelope and her butler/chauffeur Parker. Their futuristic hardware is largely developed by a genius scientist known as Brains, who lives at the International Rescue base on Tracy Island, somewhere in the Pacific.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bill Paxton, Sophia Myles, Ben Kingsley</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">action, family</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">46</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Transformer Age of Extinction</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Michael Bay</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2014</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">After an epic battle, a great city lies in ruins, but the Earth itself is saved. As humanity begins to pick up the pieces, a shadowy group emerges to try to take control of history. Meanwhile, an ancient and powerful new menace sets its sights on Earth. A new group of humans, led by Cade Yeager (Mark Wahlberg), helps Optimus Prime (Peter Cullen) and the Autobots rise up to meet their most fearsome challenge yet: a worldwide war of good versus evil.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Five Years after the Battle of Chicago, The Autobots are known now as a Threat to Humanity. A CIA Black Ops Unit known as Cemetery Wind begins hunting down the Autobots and killing them. In Texas, Inventor Cade Yeager finds a broken down old truck and decides to sell it for an Auction. He then finds out that the Broke Down Truck is Optimus Prime. Cemetery Wind then finds out Where Optimus is and Invades Yeagers Home. Yeager, His Daughter, His Daughters Boyfriend, Optimus, Bumblebee, Crosshairs, Drift and Hound are now on the run and wanted by the US Government. And to make things worse, A Bounty Hunter coming from Cybertron known as Lockdown is after Optimus and is Allies with the Government. And now They are all on the run and It's up to them to stop Lockdown and Cemetery Wind.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mark Wahlberg, Nicola Peltz, Jack reynor</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">action, sci-fi</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">47</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Transformers Dark Of The Moon</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Michael Bay</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2011</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Sam Witwicky (Shia LaBeouf) and his new girlfriend, Carly (Rosie Huntington-Whiteley), join the fray when the evil Decepticons renew their longstanding war against the Autobots. Optimus Prime (Peter Cullen) believes that resurrecting ancient Transformer Sentinel Prime (Leonard Nimoy), once the leader of the Autobots, may lead to victory. That decision, however, has devastating consequences; the war appears to tip in favor of the Decepticons, leading to a climactic battle in Chicago.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Picking up two years after the Egypt incident, the Autobots and their human allies discover a lost piece of Cybertronian technology which has been in human possession for several years. It is revealed that the artifact is part of an Autobot spacecraft which has crashed on the moon during the Apollo 11 mission to the Moon and carries a special technology and the legendary Sentinel Prime (Optimus Prime's old mentor). However, Sam Witwicky discovers a conspiracy by the Decepticons who plot to use it for their own evil purposes. And Optimus Prime finds that they are up against a menace who plans to also use it to enslave humanity in order to restore Cybertron.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Shia lebouf, Rosie Huntington-Whitely, Josh Duhmal</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">action, sci-fi</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">3</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">48</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s21"><Data ss:Type="String">Twilight</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Catherine Hardwicke</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2008</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">High-school student Bella Swan (Kristen Stewart), always a bit of a misfit, doesn't expect life to change much when she moves from sunny Arizona to rainy Washington state. Then she meets Edward Cullen (Robert Pattinson), a handsome but mysterious teen whose eyes seem to peer directly into her soul. Edward is a vampire whose family does not drink blood, and Bella, far from being frightened, enters into a dangerous romance with her immortal soulmate.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Isabella Swan moves to gloomy Forks to live with her father. As she starts her junior year in high school she becomes fascinated by Edward Cullen who holds a dark secret which is only known by his family. Edward falls in love with Bella as well but knows the further they progress in their relationship the more he is putting Bella and those close to her at risk. Edward warns Bella that she should leave him but she refuses to listen and to understand why he is saying this. Bella learns his secret. He is a vampire, however she is not afraid of his blood-thirsty needs and the fact he could kill her at any moment. Bella is afraid of losing him, the love of her life. The thrill begins when a new vampire finds it a challenge to hunt Bella down for her irresistible blood. The game is on and James will not stop until she is killed.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Kirsten Stewart, Rober Patterson, Rosalie Hale</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">drama, fantasy, teen</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2.5</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">twilight.png</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">49</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Water</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Deepa Mehta</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">2005</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The concluding part of Deepa Mehta's `elemental' trilogy of dramas examines the plight of a group of widows in late 1930s India who are forced into poverty following the deaths of their husbands. Resigned to being ignored by society, one of them breaks ranks as she tries to strike up an unlikely relationship with a follower of Mahatma Gandhi.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">A thesis picture. In 1938, Gandhi's party is making inroads in women's rights. Chuyia, a child already married but living with her parents, becomes a widow. By tradition, she is unceremoniously left at a bare and impoverished widows' ashram, beside the Ganges during monsoon season. The ashram's leader pimps out Kalyani, a young and beautiful widow, for household funds. Narayan, a follower of Gandhi, falls in love with her. Can she break with tradition and religious teaching to marry him? The ashram's moral center is Shakuntala, deeply religious but conflicted about her fate. Can she protect Kalyani or Chuyia? Amid all this water, is rebirth possible or does tradition drown all?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Lisa Ray, John Abraham, Sarala Kariyawasam</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">drama, history, romance</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">50</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Watership Down</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Martin Rosen, John Hubley</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1978</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">When a young rabbit named Fiver (Richard Briers) has a prophetic vision that the end of his warren is near, he persuades seven other rabbits to leave with him in search of a new home. Several obstacles impede their progress, including predators, a rat-filled cemetery and a speeding river. Upon arriving at their final destination, a hill dubbed Watership Down, the rabbits find that their journey is still far from over. </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Underneath a small patch of land cloaked in tall grass somewhere in a dark warren of the lush English countryside, Fiver, a skittish prescient rabbit&#45;-having shared his hauntingly vivid nightmares of destruction with his brother, Hazel&#45;-instigates a mass exodus in search of a safe new home. However, the journey to greener pastures is as long as it is precarious, entangling the audacious furry settlers in an endless string of shockingly unknown and devastating perils, which include not only voracious predators but also betrayal and the mighty weapons of men. Is this the future the Lapine pilgrims have been dreaming of at the promised Watership Down Hill, especially when the ghastly warren chief, General Woundwort, awaits at the end of the line?</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">John Hurt, Richard Briers, Zero Mostel</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">history, drama, family</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">4</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">watershipdown.png</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
  </Table>
  <WorksheetOptions xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
   <PageSetup>
    <Header x:Margin="0.3"/>
    <Footer x:Margin="0.3"/>
    <PageMargins x:Bottom="0.75" x:Left="0.7" x:Right="0.7" x:Top="0.75"/>
   </PageSetup>
   <Print>
    <ValidPrinterInfo/>
    <PaperSizeIndex>9</PaperSizeIndex>
    <HorizontalResolution>360</HorizontalResolution>
    <VerticalResolution>360</VerticalResolution>
   </Print>
   <Zoom>90</Zoom>
   <Selected/>
   <Panes>
    <Pane>
     <Number>3</Number>
     <ActiveRow>20</ActiveRow>
     <ActiveCol>1</ActiveCol>
    </Pane>
   </Panes>
   <ProtectObjects>False</ProtectObjects>
   <ProtectScenarios>False</ProtectScenarios>
  </WorksheetOptions>
 </Worksheet>
 <Worksheet ss:Name="Sheet2">
  <Table ss:ExpandedColumnCount="1" ss:ExpandedRowCount="1" x:FullColumns="1"
   x:FullRows="1" ss:DefaultColumnWidth="53" ss:DefaultRowHeight="15">
  </Table>
  <WorksheetOptions xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
   <PageSetup>
    <Header x:Margin="0.3"/>
    <Footer x:Margin="0.3"/>
    <PageMargins x:Bottom="0.75" x:Left="0.7" x:Right="0.7" x:Top="0.75"/>
   </PageSetup>
   <ProtectObjects>False</ProtectObjects>
   <ProtectScenarios>False</ProtectScenarios>
  </WorksheetOptions>
 </Worksheet>
 <Worksheet ss:Name="Sheet3">
  <Table ss:ExpandedColumnCount="1" ss:ExpandedRowCount="1" x:FullColumns="1"
   x:FullRows="1" ss:DefaultColumnWidth="53" ss:DefaultRowHeight="15">
  </Table>
  <WorksheetOptions xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
   <PageSetup>
    <Header x:Margin="0.3"/>
    <Footer x:Margin="0.3"/>
    <PageMargins x:Bottom="0.75" x:Left="0.7" x:Right="0.7" x:Top="0.75"/>
   </PageSetup>
   <ProtectObjects>False</ProtectObjects>
   <ProtectScenarios>False</ProtectScenarios>
  </WorksheetOptions>
 </Worksheet>
</Workbook>
